[{"answer": "I think he's set himself up here to cast himself in the country as victims, to characterize the campaign -- the coalition campaign as a crusader war because he thinks that's going to bring him support in the country and in the region, and he's continuing to do it.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "But what did you make of it?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "You know, this was the naval part of Tripoli harbor area, which is a pretty big area.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "What did you see there and how were you treated?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I don't put any faith in those reports.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What do you know about that?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, there was speculation on his part earlier before we saw Gadhafi's speech that perhaps he was seeking refuge in a bunker complex he apparently has built in the southern portion of the country, according to General Abd Al-Fattah Yunis.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "What are you hearing about where Gadhafi might be?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, he says that they're holding up quite well.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Did your source tell you how the opposition is holding up?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I think all we see is the military piece of it, Piers.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "General Myers, I can't really work out what's going on here, can you?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "I think it -- I'm sure it can happen.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Is that -- is that even possible that that can happen?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "You know what, that's a -- that's a great question.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Why are they pretending that they're not leading this?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well, I think any person in the military, certainly anybody in the modern military in the last couple of decades at the strategic level worries about mission creep, having an undefined mission and allowing it to creep.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Finally, General Myers, if you were running the armed forces right now in this operation, what would be the one thing you would want clarity on from President Obama?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Well, certainly there's a lot of ambiguity, uncertainty that surrounds this situation on what is the endgame.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "It's a little bit of a mess, isn't it, General Myers?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, he's missed -- he missed the opportunity, I think, very early on when the rebels were in a lean-forward mode.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Senator, why do you think President Obama has failed this test?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "I would say that this is nothing like Iraq and Afghanistan.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Can you really blame President Obama for being at the very least extremely cautious here to avoid plunged America into a third battleground following Iraq and Afghanistan, given the mess that has been caused over there?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Well, that's the real tough question.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "How do we know when we've won?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "The conversation was great, Piers.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "How was that conversation?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "So at no stage in that conversation did the President Obama express any concern that the French planes went in apparently unilaterally on Saturday without actually getting express permission of America or the rest of allies?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "The short answer is no.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Mr. Ambassador, do the French believe that Gadhafi is a legitimate target himself?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, if I may, we have to stick to the mission.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "But if he's going to go and you're blowing up his compound, isn't that sending a rather big signal that you think he is a legitimate target?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Again, we have a clear mandate of the U.N. Security Council that is about protection of the civilian population.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "And briefly, Ambassador, are you seeking regime change?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Well, let's not forget that about three weeks ago.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Well, it's about both.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Is it about people or about oil?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "It will start to starve him of money.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What effect will that have on Gadhafi and his regime?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately, this happens at a time of year when prices go higher anyway.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "And what does it mean for the average American who's worrying about how much it's going to cost to fill up their car with gas?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Are you surprised to see Colonel Gadhafi on television laughing off the NATO attacks in a rather gruesome manner?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, that's where we really need plan B now.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What if this mission fails?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "I mean, Robin Wright, never mind plan B, are you sure you know what plan A is?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Yemen is provably the next domino to fall.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "And also more pertinently, when you see what's happening in Yemen, is that not a more direct threat to American, given the very high al Qaeda presence there?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Well, Pakistan has always been the most dangerous country in the world because of its nuclear capability and because of the instability along that volatile border with Afghanistan.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "What's been going on there throughout this period?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Well, they're certainly not getting all the attention they need.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Are they getting the attention that they need in Japan?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, the government and the authorities, they need to act quickly.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Where do you even begin to start the process of rebuilding such a place?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Well, I was not experienced the world war, the -- the -- the world war, so I don't know about that.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "I mean, the Japanese have shown remarkable calm and stoicism, but there must be a point at which even the Japanese people begin to really think what is happening to us?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Well, the protests are supposed to be totally peaceful.", "docId": "110322pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "What's been going on in Syria today?", "qSentId": 493}]